<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on teraskula.com</title>
    <link>https://teraskula.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on teraskula.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:56:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://teraskula.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Open Ai, Is It Scary?</title>
      <link>https://teraskula.com/posts/chatgpt-open-ai-is-it-scary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:56:14 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraskula.com/posts/chatgpt-open-ai-is-it-scary/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT is it scary? it could be the end of yaml (kubernetes) engineers.
there is phenomenon. in this time i write this post, i just try the viral AI in a programming world. openAI just released a product, or reasearch, or a robot called chatGPT
they said
We’ve trained a model called ChatGPT which interacts in a conversational way. The dialogue format makes it possible for ChatGPT to answer followup questions, admit its mistakes, challenge incorrect premises, and reject inappropriate requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argocd Starting Up</title>
      <link>https://teraskula.com/posts/argocd-starting-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 08:48:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraskula.com/posts/argocd-starting-up/</guid>
      <description>Argo CD Starting up Recently argocd is graduated from CNCF incubating project. we already using argocd in production almost 9 months. and its working awesome.
Installation getting Started to install argocd and setting this up you could easy follow this (argocd start)[https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/getting_started/]
Lets Go I will not explain how to install or how to configure argocd but i will share my experience of using it in production in our usecase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layoff Phenomenon 2022</title>
      <link>https://teraskula.com/posts/layoff-phenomenon-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 16:38:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraskula.com/posts/layoff-phenomenon-2022/</guid>
      <description>Layoff 2022 In the end of the 2022 there is phenomenon called &amp;ldquo;massive layoff&amp;rdquo;, a lot of my friends is impacted during this time. i just wonder what is happening.
First, i am not an expert in investing, bussiness. but i kind of know (correct me if i am wrong) how to count a profit. its as simple as
income - expenses so why the company as big as GoTo or RuangGuru is layoff their employee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Is Calm Blog Engine</title>
      <link>https://teraskula.com/posts/hugo-is-calm-blog-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 17:30:15 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraskula.com/posts/hugo-is-calm-blog-engine/</guid>
      <description>Hugo x Github Pages This is my 4th time to redeploy my blog as a note for myself. deciding using hugo x ghpages because it will be just a note could be a tech note or just random thought. why hugo is calm?, because its quite simple, its static, it is fun adn quite fast (to generate).
Hugo what is hugo? Hugo is blog engine that use markdown as their main source of content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Teraskula</title>
      <link>https://teraskula.com/posts/about-teraskula/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 21:15:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraskula.com/posts/about-teraskula/</guid>
      <description>About i am prima
wong biasa, kawulane gusti Allah, anake bapak ibuk, bapake anak anak, bojone bojoku.
Teraskula.com is a new site that hopefully become my tool to release what is in my head. All this time i just blogging so someone could read my writings. this time is different. create this blog to just write what is in my mind.
so.
teras | teras, beranda, serambi, petak, anglong, tingkat in English is terrace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
