<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence on teraskula.com</title>
    <link>https://teraskula.com/categories/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on teraskula.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://teraskula.com/categories/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing AI SRE Capabilities with LangSmith: A Case Study of Cleric</title>
      <link>https://teraskula.com/posts/enhancing-ai-sre-capabilities-with-langsmith-a-case-study-of-cleric/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraskula.com/posts/enhancing-ai-sre-capabilities-with-langsmith-a-case-study-of-cleric/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an era where the digital landscape is constantly evolving, the role of Site Reliability Engineers (SREs) has become even more critical. Enter &lt;strong&gt;Cleric&lt;/strong&gt;, an AI-powered SRE that leverages cutting-edge technology to enhance its capabilities in identifying and resolving production issues. This blog post delves into how Cleric has transformed its operational efficiency by utilizing LangSmith&amp;rsquo;s continuous learning framework, ultimately showcasing the necessity of evolving AI tools to meet the demands of modern operations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the ROI of AI: Key Metrics and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://teraskula.com/posts/measuring-the-roi-of-ai-key-metrics-and-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://teraskula.com/posts/measuring-the-roi-of-ai-key-metrics-and-strategies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As organizations increasingly invest in artificial intelligence (AI), understanding the return on investment (ROI) of these initiatives becomes crucial. Measuring the ROI of AI is not a straightforward endeavor; it requires a nuanced approach that integrates both quantitative metrics and qualitative assessments. This blog post will explore effective strategies and key metrics for measuring the ROI of AI, ensuring organizations can harness the full potential of their AI investments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
